Kane Adams

Computer Games Programming Student

ABOUT ME

A games programming undergraduate student at the University of Gloucestershire that has completed the second year of my degree programme. A keen problem solver and am passionate to further develop my programming knowledge and gain industry experience working with diverse teams as part of student placement. My skills in problem-solving and teamwork have allowed me to receive a first in one of my university assignments.

EDUCATION

- BSc Computer Games Programming, University of Gloucestershire (September 2018 - Present)
 - During this course I have gained proficiency in programming in C++ and C# and a solid understanding in mathematics of games development. Strong level of familiarity with the Unity games engine. Working individually and within teams to create games for many platforms.
- A-Levels, Ashlyns School (September 2013 June 2018)
 - 2 A-Levels and 1 AS-level
 - Level 3 EPQ, focused on website production
 - 8 GCSEs, A in Mathematics

RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

- After-school Coding Club Tutor, Komplete Genius (October 2016 - July 2018)
 - Taught Scratch and basic Lua (Roblox) to children, led sessions once turned 18, DBS checked
 - Created 20 lesson plans for Scratch
- Coding Club Tutor, Rocket Coders (October 2017 -December 2017)
 - Taught basic web development (HTML, CSS), robotics (Arduino) and Stencyl 2D game development to children
- IT Technician, Marston Group (August 2017)
 - Spend 2 weeks work experience at IT support
 - Repaired laptops, managed software on laptops and tablets
 - Helped reprogram body cameras
 - Shadowed software team
 - Originally 1 week work experience, invited back for second week for merit

Address: Hertfordshire, United Kingdom

Mobile: 07806812234

Email: kaneadams.ka23@gmail.com
Portfolio: kaneadamsportfolio.com
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/kane23
GitHub: github.com/KaneA23

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- High level of proficiency with *Unity Games Engine*
- Competent programming knowledge in C# and C++ used in the Visual Studio
- Version Control experience with GitHub and Perforce
- Skills in testing and Debugging where I have fixed errors in mine and other people's code
- Can use the Agile Methodology to create projects
- Experience developing for Android

SOFT SKILLS

- Teamwork, with working as part of a group, we were able to achieve a first in an assignment
- Problem-solving with use of research
- Management through appointing jobs in the games development community

INDUSTRY BASED INTERESTS

- I enjoy playing video games, catalysing my interest in games development where I work on personal projects and in communities away from university.
- I have a keen interest in PC hardware where I build, repair and upgrade my friends and families' computers, using research to ensure they meet user specifications and future requirements.

OTHER HOBBIES

 I have an interest in martial arts, with a first-degree black belt, and came third in two regional tournament events in Shotokan Karate after 10 years. I am also the president of the Taekwondo society at university, where I have the responsibilities of communicating with external instructors and other societies, as well as arranging events.